A Guide to the Richmond (Va.) Office of the City Engineer, Records, 1809-1975
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Architectural drawings and plans, 1809-1975.
  - Street - Plan of / 34th Street / from / Broad St. to 'P' St., 23-A-6, 1909, Dimensions: 12 x 35-1/2 in. - 31 x 90 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 75)
  - Street - Plan Showing Route of Christian St. / and Oakwood Ave. & Canepa St. Sewers, 55-B-2, 1909, Dimensions: 22-1/4 x 30 in. - 56 x 76 cm.; Scale: 1" = 100'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 72)
  - Street - Map / of / Proposed Extension / of / Preston Street / Between 5th and 6th Streets, 61-B-1, 1909, Dimensions: 19 x 36 n. - 48 x 91 cm.; Scale: 1" = 30'; Media: India ink, red ink, and yellow ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 68)
  - Street - Plan / Showing Proposed Extension of / Sheppard Street, [No file number], 1909, Dimensions: 32 x 37-1/4 in. - 81 x 95 cm.; Scale: 1" = 50'; Media: India ink and blue ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 72)
    Drawn By: J. Thompson Brown & Co. / Agents for Owners
  - Street - Plan of West Side of 34th St. / from / Clay St. to Leigh St., 23-A-6, 1909, Dimensions: 18-1/2 x 13-1/2 in. - 47 x 34 cm.; Scale: 1" = 30'; Media: India ink and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 75)
  - Street - A sketch showing the West line of 8th Street, 24-A-6, 1910, Dimensions: 12-1/2 x 33-1/4 in. - 32 x 86 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: Pencil, India ink, and red ink on heavy paper; Sheets: 1 (Folder 75)
    Drawn By: P. P. Taliaferro / Asst. Engr
  - Street - Map of The S.E. Cor of 12th.& Franklin Sts. / and Vicinity / Showing the Proposed Rounding off of that / Corner and Property to be Acquired, 86-C-2, 1910, Dimensions: 22-1/2 x 36 in. - 57 x 91 cm.; Scale: 1" = 10'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 64)
    Drawn By: City Engineer's Office / Richmond, Va. / Fontaine Jones Asst. Eng'r.
  - Street - Chart Showing Changes in grades / Recommended for Streets / Between / Boulevard & Cleveland St. / Floyd Ave. & Leonard St., 34-C-3, 1910, Dimensions: 22 x 29-1/2 in. - 56 x 75 cm.; Scale: 1" = 100'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 72)
  - Street - Plan of Streets & Alleys / West of Boulevard / between / Broad St., Monument Ave., & Franklin St., 33-C-3, 1910, Dimensions: 24-1/2 x 35-1/4 in. - 62 x 89 cm.; Scale: 1" = 100'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 72)
  - Street - Profile and Grade of Pleasants St. from Mosby St. to 19th. St, 64-A-2, 1910, Dimensions: 13-3/4 x 43 in. - 35 x 109 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: Blueprint; Sheets: 1 (Folder 66)
  - Street - [Plans of proposed street connecting Pleasants Street to Marshall Street showing adjoining lot owners], 40-B-3, 1910, Dimensions: 37-1/4 x 20-3/4 in. - 94 x 53 cm.; Scale: 1" = 40'; Media: India ink, red ink, and yellow ink on linen; Sheets: 2 (Folder 70)
    Drawn By: Chas. E. Bolling / City Engineer and as such / City Surveyor
  - Street - City of Richmond Va. / Plat of the North Line of Marshall St. / between / 12th St and Marshall St. Viaduct, 68-A-2, 1911, Dimensions: 11 x 33-1/4 in. - 28 x 84 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 77)
  - Street - City of Richmond Va. / Plan of Lester Street / from / Poplar St. Southwardly, 46-B-3, 1911, Dimensions: 16-3/4 x 30 in. - 43 x 76 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: Pencil and India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 70)
    Drawn By: Office of City Engineer / Survey and Plan by / Fontaine Jones / Asst. Eng.
  - Street - Plan Showing Triangular Piece of Land Proposed to be / Acquired from J.H. & E.J. Lyneman for Opening & Improvement / of 19th St. from Marshall St. to Pleasants St., 40-B-3, 1911, Dimensions: 12-3/4 x 10 in. - 32 x 25 cm.; Scale: 1" = 40'; Media: Pencil, India ink, red ink, and yellow ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 69)
  - Street - Map of Seventh St. / from / Semmes St. to James River, 64-B-1, 1912, Dimensions: 22-1/2 x 35-1/2 in. - 57 x 90 cm.; Scale: 1" = 50'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 71)
  - Street - City of Richmond, Va. / Cary Street / Between / Meadow & Lombardy St. / Showing the Present and Proposed South / Line of Cary St., 74-A-2, 1912, Dimensions: 14 x 47-1/2 in. - 36 x 121 cm.; Scale: 1" = 40'; Media: Pencil, India ink, red ink and yellow ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 77)
    Drawn By: Office of City Eng'r.
  - Street - Section / of / Cary Street / from. Boulevard to Corporation Line, 66-A-1, 1912, Dimensions: 13-1/2 x 34 in. - 34 x 86 cm.; Scale: 1" = 2'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 77)
  - Street - Plan for Opening Preston Street from / 5th to 6th Sts.With Names of Owners of Property., 61-B-1, 1912, Dimensions: 19 x 16-1/4 in. - 48 x 41 cm.; Scale: 1" = 30'; Media: India ink and yellow ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 68)
  - Street - City of Richmond Va. / Map / of / Blocks Bounded / by / Taylor, Linden, Beverly & Harrison Sts., 46-C-2a, 1912, Dimensions: 20-1/2 x 28 in. - 52 x 71 cm.; Scale: 1" = 50'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 76)
  - Street - Line of Occupation of the South Line of Bank St, 63-A-1a, 1912, Dimensions: 17 x 38-3/4 in. - 43 x 98 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 67)
    Drawn By: City Engineer's Office / Richmond, Va. / Fontaine Jones A.C.E.
  - Street - Fifteenth Street / between / Broad and Marshall Sts. / Plan of Proposed Opening Of., 73-A-2, 1912, Dimensions: 14 x 41-1/4 in. - 35 x 105 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: Pencil and India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 76)
  - Street - Map / Showing the Grass Plats on Monument Ave. from Lombardy St. / to the Boulevard, 75-A-2, 1912, Dimensions: 10-1/4 x 27-3/4 in. - 26 x 70 cm.; Scale: 1" = 200; Media: India ink and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 77)
  - Street - Plan of Main St. from 8th. To 10th. St. / Showing Lines of Occupation, 60-A-1, 1912, Dimensions: 14-1/2 x 33 in. - 37 x 84 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: India ink on linen with pencil notations; Sheets: 1 (Folder 67)
  - Street - Map / Showing Property Owners / Adjacent to / Monument Ave. Extended / Henrico Co. Va., 50-B-4, 1912, Dimensions: 12 x 22 in. - 30 x 56 cm.; Scale: None; Media: Blueprint; Sheets: 1 (Folder 75)
    Drawn By: T. Crawford Redd & Bro. / Surveyors & Engrs.
  - Street - Map of W. S. Forbes' Property / on th Roseneath Road, showing pro- / posed Extension of Monument Avenue / and other Streets through the same, 51-B-4, 1912, Dimensions: 22-1/4 x 22-1/2 in. 56 x 57 cm.; Scale: 1" = 150'; Media: Blueprint; Sheets: 1 (Folder 75)
    Drawn By: T. Crawford Redd & Bro. / Surveyors & Engineer
  - Street - Section / of / Beverly Street / from / Meadow Street to the Boulevard, 62-A-1b, 1912, Dimensions: 10-1/4 x 26-3/4 in. - 27 x 68 cm.; Scale: 1" = 2'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 67)
  - Street - Section / of / Beverly Street / from / Randolph to Meadow Street, 62-A-1a, 1912, Dimensions: 10-1/4 x 26-3/4 in. - 27 x 68 cm.; Scale: 1" = 2'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 67)
  - Street - Section / of / Broad Street / Between / Sixth & Seventh Sts., 61-A-1, 1912, Dimensions: 16-1/4 x 65 in. - 41 x 165 cm.; Scale: 1" = 2'; Media: India ink and colored inks on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 67)
  - Street - City of Richmond Va / Elevation of Lester St. / Map, Profile, Plans and Sections of / Walls and Steps, 51-B-3, 1912, Dimensions: 18-1/2 x 24 in. - 47 x 61 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: India ink, red ink, and yellow ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 70)
    Drawn By: City Eng'r's Office / Richmond, Va / Fontaine Jones / Ass't Eng'r
  - Street - Plan Showing Property Owners on Cary St. / Bet. Allen and Boulevard with / Cuts and Fills along said Street., 57-C-2, 1913, Dimensions: 36 x 42 in. - 91 x 106 cm.; Scale: 1" = 40'; Media: Pencil and India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 72)
    Drawn By: Office of City Engineer - Richmond, VA.
  - Street - Map Showing Proposed Widening of Sidewalk / on East Side of Ninth Street from / Stockton to Maury St., 89-A-2, 1913, Dimensions: 9-3/4 x 41-1/4 in. - 25 x 105 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 76)
  - Street - City of Richmond, Va. / Map of that Portion of a Proposed / Riverside Drive / between / Gambles Hill and Riverside parks, 52-C-2, 1913, Dimensions: 41 x 36-1/2 in. - 104 x 92 cm.; Scale: 1" = 50'; Media: India ink and colored inks on linen with pencil notations; Sheets: 1 (Folder 72)
  - Street - Map of the Intersection of / Old & New Lester St. at Nicholson St. / Showing the Proposed Alignment of / Street Railway Tracks, 53-C-2, 1913, Dimensions: 25-3/4 x 34 in. - 66 x 87 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 2 (Folder 72)
  - Street - City of Richmond, Va. / Map of / Territory Bounded by / S St. and Northern Corporation Line, 30th St., Stewart St. and Oakwood Ave., 62-C-3, 1913, Dimensions:; Scale: 1" = 50'; Media: Pencil, India ink, and colored inks on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 72)
    Drawn By: City Engineer's Office / Richmond, VA/
  - Street - Map Showing Proposed Widening of Bainbridge Street, 54-C-2, 1913, Dimensions: 18 x 36-1/4 in. - 46 x 92 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: India ink and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 72)
  - Street - Plan of the / proposed widening of Cary Street / form Temple to Addison, Showing / Property-owners bordering on / same, and how they will be affected / by the change, 96-A-2, 1913, Dimensions: 17 x 89 in. - 43 x 126 cm.; Scale: 1" = 30'; Media: India ink and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 76)
  - Street - Plan of the East Side of First Street / Between Broad and Marshall Streets / Showing True Line and Line of Occupation, 91-A-2, 1913, Dimensions: 13 x 38-3/4 in. - 33 x 98 cm.; Scale: 1" = 10'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 76)
  - Street - Plat Showing Occupation of Property / on th east Side of First Street, Between Broad / and Marshall Streets; Richmond, Va., 91-A-2b, 1913, Dimensions: 9 x 25-1/2 in. - 23 x 65 cm.; Scale: 1" = 15'; Media: Blueprint; Sheets: 1 (Folder 76)
    Drawn By: T. Crawford Redd & Bros. / Surveyors Engrs.
  - Street - Map / of / Blocks Bounded by / Taylor, Linden, Beverly, & Harrison Sts. / Chart of Revised Grades, 46-C-2c, 1913, Dimensions: 22-1/2 x 26-1/2 in. - 57 x 67 cm.; Scale: 1" = 50'; Media: India ink and red ink on linen with pencil notations; Sheets: 1 (Folder 74)
  - Street - Plan showing grade elevations on / South Harrison St. between Marshall / Reservoir and Riverview Cemetery, 83-A-2, 1913, Dimensions: 16 x 37-1/2 in. -; Scale: 1" = 40'; Media: India ink and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 77)
  - Street - Plan / of the / South Side of Cary St. / Between / Meadow St. and Addison St, 97-A-2, 1913, Dimensions: 12-3/4 x 41-3/4 in. - 32 x 106 cm.; Scale: 1" = 30'; Media: India ink and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 76)
  - Street - Map Showing New Proposed East Line of / Cowardin Avenue from Porter to Semmes Streets, 90-A-2, 1913, Dimensions: 15-1/2 x 66-1/2 in. - 39 x 169 cm.; Scale: None; Media: India ink on linen with pencil notations; Sheets: 1 (Folder 76)
  - Street - Plan Showing Elevations of / Curbs, Gutters & Railway Tracks / on / Robinson St. from Monument to Kensington Aves., 87-A-2, 1913, Dimensions: 16-1/2 x 77-3/4 in. - 42 x 197 cm.; Scale: 1" = 10'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 76)
  - Street - Map of Cary St. from South Lombardy to Addison St. / Showing the Property to be Acquired for a Proposed Widening / to a Sixty Foot Street, 79-A-2, 1913, Dimensions: 16-1/4 x 36 in. - 41 x 92 cm.; Scale: 1" = 100'; Media: India ink and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 77)
  - Street - Plan of 25th St. from Venable to R St. / Showing Damage and Improvement to Property, 78-A-2, 1913, Dimensions: 16-1/4 x 40-1/2 in. - 41 x 103 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: Blueprint; Sheets: 1 (Folder 77)
  - Street - Map of Williamsburg Ave. / from / 10th St to National Cemetery / Showing Proposed Widening to Fifty Feet, 101-A-2, 1914, Dimensions: 15 x 54-1/2 in. - 38 x 138 cm.; Scale: 1" = 100'; Media: Pencil, India ink, red ink, and yellow ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 77)
  - Street - City of Richmond, Va. / Map of Territory / Bounded by / Boulevard and Sheppard St. / Cary St. and Beverly St. / Showing a Proposed Opening, 65-C-2, 1914, Dimensions: 28 x 32 in. - 71 x 81 cm.; Scale: 1" = 50'; Media: India ink on linen with colored ink notation; Sheets: 1 (Folder 72)
  - Street - Plan for the Opening of Lady Street / from Beverly to Blair St. / Showing that Portion from Beverly to Ashland St. / Names of Property Owners, property to be Acquired, 98-A-2, 1914, Dimensions: 16 x 50-3/4 in. - 41 x 129 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 77)
  - Street - Map / of / Seventh St from Semmes to Ninth St Bridge / Showing New Proposed Curve Lines, 77-C-2, 1914, Dimensions: 18-1/2 x 50 in. - 47 x 123 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: Pencil and India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 72)
  - Street - Profile and Proposed Grade of Alleys from / West St. to Roseneath Road Between Park Ave. and Leonard St., 79-C-2, 1914, Dimensions: 19-1/4 x 38 in. - 49 x 96 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: India ink and yellow ink on linen graph paper; Sheets: 1 (Folder 64)
  - Street - Paving With Bricks the North and South Sides of Leigh St. from Lombardy St. West, 10184-B-1, 1914, Dimensions: 17-1/2 x 40-1/4 in. - 44 x 102 cm.; Scale: None; Media: Pencil and India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 71)
  - Street - Extension of 15th Street / Under Broad Street / Foundation Plan for Arch and Retaining Walls, 83-C-2(b), 1914, Dimensions: 27-1/4 x 41-1/4 in. - 69 x 105 cm.; Scale: 1/4" = 1'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 3 (Folder 64)
    Drawn By: City Engineer's Office / Richmond, Va. / (L.L.B.).
  - Street - Plan Showing Proposed Curb Construction / At the Northeast Corner of / Nicholson Street, 88-C-2, 1914, Dimensions: 22-1/2 x 30-1/4 in. - 57 x 77 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: Pencil and India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 64)
    Drawn By: Office of City Engineer / Richmond, Virginia / G.M. Bowers, Asst. Engr.
  - Street - Center Line Profile of / Redd St., Coalter St. to Mechanicsville Turnpike, 80-C-2, 1914, Dimensions: 20-1/4 x 37 in. - 52 x 94 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: India ink on linen graph paper; Sheets: 1 (Folder 64)
  - Street - Map of Lester St. from Poplar to Nicholson St. / Showing Location of Sand Basins, 42-C-3, 1914, Dimensions: 21-1/4 x 35-3/4 in. - 54 x 89 cm.; Scale: 1" = 50'; Media: Ink and colored inks on paper with cloth backing; Sheets: 1 (Folder 75)
  - Street - Plan Showing Property Owners on Hull Street / from 7th to 12th Streets / for Allegations for Granolithic Sidewalk Paving, 99-A-2, 1914, Dimensions: 9-1/4 x 44-3/4 in. - 23 x 113 cm.; Scale: 1" = 40'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 76)
    Drawn By: D. F. LaPrade, Asst. City Eng.
  - Street - Center Line Profile / of / Lester St. from Denny to Nicholson Street / Showing Present and Proposed Grades, 87-C-2, 1914, Dimensions: 22-3/4 x 31 in. - 58 x 79 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: India ink on linen graph paper; Sheets: 1 (Folder 64)
  - Street - Plan of Block Between Cary & / Taylor & Meadow & Granby Sts. / Showing Proposed Alley to be / Opened., 85-C-2, 1914, Dimensions: 22 x 31-1/4 in. - 56 x 79 cm.; Scale: 1" = 30'; Media: India ink on linen with pencil notation; Sheets: 1 (Folder 64)
    Drawn By: City Engineer's Office / Richmond, Va. / Fontaine Jones Asst. Engr.
  - Street - Dock St. from 14th. St. to 17th St. / Profile over center line of Proposed 20 ft. covered / channel for the Dock., 68-C-2a, 1915, Dimensions: 12-1/2 x 39 in. - 32 x 99 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: Pencil and India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 72)
  - Street - Roseneath Road / Proposed Widening of, to th Width of 80 ft. / from / Grove Ave. to Broad St., 69-A-2, 1915, Dimensions: 13-3/4 x 51-1/4 in. - 35 x 129 cm.; Scale: 1" = 100'; Media: Pencil, India ink, and yellow ink on linen; Sheets: 3 (Folder 77)
  - Street - Plan & Section / of / Monument Avenue / Showing the Proposed Extension of / Monument Ave. / under the / R. F. & P. Belt Line R. R., 50-C-3, 1915, Dimensions: 18-1/2 x 35 in. - 47 x 89 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: India ink and colored pencils on paper with cloth backing; Sheets: 1 (Folder 75)
  - Street - Richmond, Virginia / Retaining Wall along the East Line of Lombardy St. / on the property of the Sitterding Carneal Davis Company, 92-C-2, 1915, Dimensions: 19-1/4 x 41-1/4 in. - 49 x 105 cm.; Scale: 1/4" = 1'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 64)
  - Street - Plan, Elevation & Detail / of /Galvanized Iron Pipe Hand Rail / To Be Built On The West Side of Fourteenth St. / from / James River to a Point About 230ft. North, 103-C-2, 1915, Dimensions: 24-3/4 x 38 in. - 63 x 97 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: India ink and blue ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 64)
  - Street - Chart of Ginter Park / Showing Defective Sidewalk Work / Done Under Contract With / K.L. Black & Co., 101-C-2, 1915, Dimensions: 27-1/4 x 40-1/2 in. - 69 x 103 cm.; Scale: 1" = 200'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 71)
    Drawn By: City Engr's Office / Richmond, Virginia / G.M. Bowers, Asst. City Engr.
  - Street - Plan and Profile / of / Proposed Chamberlayne Ave. (1000 ft. wide) / from / Graham St. to Baker St., 47-A-6, 1915, Dimensions: 25 x 72-1/2 in. - 64 x 184 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: India ink, red ink, and yellow ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 67)
    Drawn By: City Engineers Office - Richmond, Va. / M. O. Hankins Asst. Engr.
  - Street - Chart Showing Grades for Car Tracks on / 31st. Bet. M and O Sts., 93-C-2, 1915, Dimensions: 13 x 32-3/4 in. - 33 x 83 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: India ink and red ink on linen with pencil notations; Sheets: 1 (Folder 64)
  - Street - Plan for Proposed Widening of 25th. St. / From S Street to Corporation Line, 91-C-2, 1915, Dimensions: 21 x 36 in. - 53 x 92 cm.; Scale: 1" = 30'; Media: India ink on linen with pencil notatons; Sheets: 1 (Folder 64)
    Drawn By: City Engineer's Office / Richmond, Virginia / Fontaine Jones / Ass't City Engr.
  - Street - Plan of Grace St. / Between / Harrison and Shaffer Sts. / Showing Location of Houses and Elevation / of same above Curb Grade, 102-C-2, 1915, Dimensions: 28-1/2 x 38 in. - 72 x 97 cm.; Scale: [1" = 20']; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 64)
  - Street - Plan of Streets and Alleys / Proposed to be Dedicated to / City of Richmond / by / Edwin Pleasants, 79-B-1, 1915, Dimensions: 23-1/2 x 31 in. -60 x 80 cm.; Scale: 1" = 100'; Media: 1 India ink and colored inks on linen, 1 blueprint; Sheets: 2 (Folder 70)
    Drawn By: City Engineer's Office / E.J.K.
  - Street - Profile of 14th. Street From N.S. of Cary St. to Mayo's Bridge., 106-C-2, 1915, Dimensions: 23-3/4 x 60 in. - 60 x 152 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: India ink on linen graph paper; Sheets: 1 (Folder 64)
    Drawn By: P.P. Taliaferro / Asst. Engr
  - Street - Profile of Alleys Bounded by Grove, Floyd, / Harvie and Plum Sts., 16-D-3, 1915, Dimensions: 11-1/2 x 20-1/4 in. - 29 x 51 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: Pencil, India ink, and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 66)
  - Street - Map of that Portion of Marshall Square / Adjacent to Williamsburg Ave. and Elm Street / Showing the Proposed New Location of Elm St., 98-C-2, 1915, Dimensions: 30-1/4 x 30-1/2 in. - 77 x 77 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: Pencil and India ink on linen with pencil notations; Sheets: 1 (Folder 64)
  - Street - Plan and Profiles / of / Catherine St. Between Mumford and Henry, 94-C-2, 1915, Dimensions: 22-1/2 x 43 in. - 57 x 109 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: India ink on linen tracing paper; Sheets: 1 (Folder 64)
  - Street - A Plan for the Reconstruction of the / Curb and Gutter on the West Side of 5th St. / Southwardly from Byrd St., 89-B-1, 1916, Dimensions: 20 x 31 in. - 51 x 79 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: Pencil, India ink, and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 71)
  - Street - Map Showing Proposed Opening of / Louisiana Street, 80-B-1, 1916, Dimensions: 21-3/4 x 34-1/4 in.- 55 x 87 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: Pencil, India ink, and yellow ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 70)
  - Street - Plan and Center Line Profiles of Colorado Ave. / Meade, Eggleston, Lombardy & Sumpter Sts., 114-C-2, 1916, Dimensions: 24-1/4 x 33 in. - 62 x 84 c.; Scale: Various; Media: Pencil and India ink on linen graph paper; Sheets: 1 (Folder 64)
    Drawn By: City Eng'r's Office / Richmond, Virginia / Fontaine Jones / Ass't City Engr.
  - Street - Sketch Showing the Reduction of 11th. St. From / Bank to Main by 15ft. Driveway for Post Office, 113-C-2, 1916, Dimensions: 28-1/2 x 49-3/4 in. - 72 x 126 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: India ink and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 64)
    Drawn By: City Engineer's Office / Richmond, Va. / W.P. Gwathmey. / Droughtsman.
  - Street - Plan of Block Bounded by Grace, Franklin, 8th and 9th Streets / Showing True Lines of Streets and Lines by Occupation, 82-B-1, 1916, Dimensions: 32 x 26 in. - 81 x 66 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: India ink, red ink, and yellow ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 70)
  - Street - Plan Showing Location of Buildings / at / Perry and Fifteenth Streets, Richmond, Va., 86-B-1, 1916, Dimensions: 18 x 35-3/4 in. - 46 x 91 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: India ink and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 70)
    Drawn By: City Engineer's Office / D.F. LaPrade / A.C.E.
  - Street - Plan of Block Bounded by Broad, Grace, / Jefferson and Adams Showing Property / Owners and Encroachments in Alley, 88-B-1, 1916, Dimensions: 22 x 27 in. - 56 x 69 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: India ink and yellow ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 70)
  - Street - Chamberlayne Parkway / Plan Showing the Proposed Location Through / C.G. Schwalm's Property, 87-B-1, 1916, Dimensions: 25-1/2 x 40-3/4 in. - 65 x 104 cm.; Scale: 1" = 50'; Media: India ink and yellow ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 70)
  - Street - Map of Block Bounded By / R.F.& P. R.R. Bowe, Broad & McKenzie Sts / Showing the Location of R.F.& P.R.R. Co's Spur-Tracks / on Railroad Ave., 115-C-2, 1916, Dimensions: 23 x 40-1/2 in. - 58 x 103 cm.; Scale: 1" = 40'; Media: Pencil, India ink and red ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 64)
  - Street - Plan of House Numbers on N/S/ Leigh St. Bet. / Elizabeth and Dinneen Sts., 113-A-2, 1916, Dimensions: 10 x 34-1/4 in. - 25 x 87 cm.; Scale: 1" = 30'; Media: India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 76)
  - Street - Chamberlayne Parkway / Proposed Location of Parkway / from / Graham Road to Calhoun St., 46-A-6, 1916, Dimensions: 23 x47 in. - 58 x 119 cm.; Scale: 1" = 100'; Media: 2 Blueprints with pencil notations (damaged), 1 fragmentary blueprint; Sheets: 3 (Folder 65)
    Drawn By: Surveys & Map By / Bolton Clarke & Pratt Inc. / Civil Engineers Richmond, VA.
  - Street - Plan of Exchange Alley / by Actual Survey, 72-B-1, 1916, Dimensions: 25-1/2 x 30-1/2 in. - 65 x 77 cm.; Scale: 1" = 20'; Media: Pencil and India ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 70)
    Drawn By: City Engineer's Office / Richmond, Va. / J.N. Eubank, / Asst. City Eng,
  - Street - Map Showing / Owners on East and West Sidesof Hague St. and the West Sideof Nicholson St, 84-B-1, 1916, Dimensions: 33-1/2 x 34-1/2 in. - 85 x 88 cm.; Scale: 1" = 30'; Media: India ink and colored inks on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 70)
    Drawn By: City Engineer's Office / Richmond, Va. / Fontaine Jones Ast. Eng'r
  - Street - Map and Center Line Profile / of / Meadow Street / from / Ashland St. to Colorado Ave., 76-B-1, 1916, Dimensions: 19-3/4 x 32-1/2 in. - 50 x 83 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: Pencil, India ink, and yellow ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 70)
  - Street - Map of The Block Bounded By / Dance, Harrison, Ashland, and Randolph Sts., 77-B-1, 1916, Dimensions: 18 x 28-3/4 in. - 46 x 73 cm.; Scale: 1" = 40'; Media: Pencil, India ink, red ink, and yellow ink on linen; Sheets: 1 (Folder 70)